

Veronica. Backend Developer

+6287888302321

veyolie@gmail.com

linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/veronica-

a245a6197/

Tangerang, Indonesia

SUMMARY

I am very interested in developing an application or website. I love to learn more about developing an application or website. I want to search for more experience in the IT field because it's fun to study more about programming. I am very open to new knowledge in the IT field. Now I am focus on learning Backend Developer

am very interested in developing an application or website. I love to learn more about developing an application or website. I want to search for more experience in the IT field because it's fun to study more about programming. I am very open to new knowledge in the IT field. Now I am focus on learning Backend Developer.

EXPERIENCE

06/2022 - 12/2022

Backend developer (Fintech)

PT. Finpoint Solusi Indonesia

Work as a backend developer as a restful API developer for website development and develop generating report program using Golang programing language.

- Develop a payment gateway and backend website program using Golang programming language and PostgreSQL as the Database.
- Understanding using docker and deploying program at the server.
- Understand how to use Elasticsearch to get transactions and generate a report.

01/2022 - 06/2022

Assistant Laboratory (Visual Programming)

Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

Teaching Visual Programming in Universitas Multimedia Nusantara using Visual Studio.

- learned more about using the C# language
- I also learned about working together with my partner and building communication in class.
- · Learning about how to transfer knowledge to the other student.

08/2021 - 12/2021

Assistant Laboratory (Probability Statistic)

Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

Teaching Probability Statistics in University Multimedia Nusantara using R Studio.

- Learned how to work together with my partner
- · learn more about R, have a good experience in teaching
- · have a good experience in teaching and communicate with the student

EDUCATION

2023

Information System

Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

Bachelor Degree

I am a system information student at Universitas Multimedia Nusantara with a GPA 3.72. Studying database oracle, building websites and applications, learning how to read flowcharts for apps and businesses, and data visualization.

CERTIFICATES

10/2020 - Present

Gajiku First Place and Public Favorite at Startup Weekend

SKILLS

Golang Intermediate Figma Beginner Java Beginner SQL Beginner HTML Intermediate phpmyadmin Intermediate Intermediate PostgreSQL Intermediate C# Intermediate CSS Beginner Oracle Tableau PHP Beginner Beginner

Docker Intermediate

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Intermediate English Basic